Ryan Syme

Freelance Web Developer

Dalbyvägen 50a 761 54, Norrtälje ryansyme@outlook.com (+46) 70 037 6163

SUMMARY

During my career, I have developed several skills in working with both computers and numbers I have the ability to properly manage, organize and analyze information and present that information in a clear and concise manner. I have worked in many different positions, including managerial positions and have experience in working alone, within a group and as a leader.

EDUCATION

Sep 2020 - Feb 2021 Full-Stack Web Development

Code Institute, Dublin

Jan 2020 - May 2020 Web Development 1

Web Development 2
NTI Komvux, Norrtälje

Aug 2012 - Mar 2014 Accounting 1

Accounting 2
Business Economy 1
Business Economy 2
Computer Science

Computer and Network Technology

NTI Komvux, Norrtälje

Sep 1996 - May 1998 Statistics

Physics Biology

Palmers College, Grays, England

SKILLS

Front End HTML CSS JavaScript

JQuery Bootstrap

Back-End Python Django Flask

MongoDB SQL / NoSQL

Assets XD GitHub GitPod

Balsamiq Gimp

EMPLOYMENT

Feb 2021 - Ongoing

Full-Stack Web Developer

Entre preneurship

Freelance Full-Stack Web Developer

Web Design

Front-End Development

Back-End Development

Available for both individual and group collaborations.

Jun 2018 - Dec 2020

CAD Designer

SymeCAD

Freelance computer-assisted design of rooms, for construction and remodeling companies to show virtual presentation booklets of their remodels to customers

Responsible for all aspects of a CAD Design Company including:

CAD Design
Customer Service
Time Management
Accounting

May 2014 - Aug 2015

Entrepreneur

Nordic Glow Ltd

Responsible for all aspects of an Internet E-Cigarette Company including:

Product Design Customer Service Budgeting and Accounting Purchasing and Sales

May 2008 - Aug 2012

Poker Professional

Entrepreneur

Professional Poker Player with many important skills and attributes are needed including:

Performing data analysis to calculate profitability Solving logic problems with incomplete information Performing calculations for risk analysis Thinking methodical whilst under pressure

Jun 2003 - Apr 2008

Deputy Manager

Coral Racing

Deputy Manager in a Bookmaker with responsibility for the store, staff and customers. Tasks included:

Calculation of customer winnings

Handling and accounting for large sums of money

Training of new employees

Bookkeeping and inventory management

Apr 1998 - Jun 2003

Cashier

 $Coral\ Racing$

Cashier in a Bookmaker. Tasks included:

Customer Service
Data registration

Responsibility for the Cash Register